Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee Theatre Collection, 1901- AR.0235
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Faculty Players, 1901-1943; IV; (Playbills, Administratives Materials, and Contracts)
  - Newsletters, 1939-1942; D
    - Ye Playebill, Faculty Players Newsletter, 1940-1942 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - The University of Tennessee Newsletter, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Official Bulletin of the Tennessee Association of Non-professional Theatres, 1941-1942 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Other Materials, circa 1942-1943; E
    - Prompt Cards and Miscellaneous Notes, circa 1943 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Non-UT Theatre Materials, circa 1942 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Special Events and Guest Contributors, 1973 May 27-2009 September 20; V
  - Special Events, 1973 May 27-2009 September 20; A; (Programs, Photographs, and Production/Financial/Marketing Materials)
    - Clarence Brown Film Festival, 1973 May 27-29; (1 of 5); (Programs and Brochures) (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Clarence Brown Film Festival, 1973 May 27-29; (2 of 5); (Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Clarence Brown Film Festival, 1973 May 27-29; (3 of 5); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Clarence Brown Film Festival, 1973 May 27-29; (4 of 5); (Negatives) (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Clarence Brown Film Festival, 1973 May 27-29; (5 of 5); (PSAs and Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - A Spring Film Festival, 1974 March 28-30; (1 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - A Spring Film Festival, 1974 March 28-30; (2 of 2); (Box Office/Financial Materials) (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - UT Theatres Costume Auction, 1980-1993; (1 of 5; 1980); (PSAs, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - UT Theatres Costume Auction, 1980-1993; (2 of 5; 1981); (Flyers, Press Clippings, and Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - UT Theatres Costume Auction, 1980-1993; (3 of 5; 1987); (PSAs, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - UT Theatres Costume Auction, 1980-1993; (4 of 5; 1988); (Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - UT Theatres Costume Auction, 1980-1993; (5 of 5; 1993); (Press Clippings and PSAs) (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre 10th Anniversary Gala, 1981 February 6; (1 of 2); (Press Clippings, PSAs, and RSVPs) (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre 10th Anniversary Gala, 1981 February 6; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Southeastern Theatre Conference (SETC), 1982-1999; (Press Clippings, PSAs, and Planning Materials) (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Royal Shakespeare Company Residency, 1984 October 16-18; (1 of 3); (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Royal Shakespeare Company Residency, 1984 October 16-18; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Royal Shakespeare Company Residency, 1984 October 16-18; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Adolphe Appia: Performer, Space, Light, 1985 September 16-October 5; (Press Clippings and PSAs) (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Guess Who's Coming to the Theatre? The Theatre's Future Audience Conference, 1986 February 7-8; (Programs, Press Clippings, and PSAs) (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - American College Theatre Festival, Region IV, 1987 February 17-21; (1 of 3); (Programs and Performance Critiques) (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - American College Theatre Festival, Region IV, 1987 February 17-21; (2 of 3); (Publicity and Press) (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - American College Theatre Festival, Region IV, 1987 February 17-21; (3 of 3); (Planning and Event Management Materials) (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Warsaw Tango (Teatro del Sur), 1988 April 28-30; (1 of 3); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Warsaw Tango (Teatro del Sur), 1988 April 28-30; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Warsaw Tango (Teatro del Sur), 1988 April 28-30; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Formal at the Farm, 1991 May 3; (Invitation and Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Carousel Theatre 40th Anniversary, 1991 May 3-June 9; (1 of 2); (Flyers and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Carousel Theatre 40th Anniversary, 1991 May 3-June 9; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Castaways (Diablomundo), 1993 September 16-19; (1 of 4); (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Castaways (Diablomundo), 1993 September 16-19; (2 of 4); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Castaways (Diablomundo), 1993 September 16-19; (3 of 4); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Castaways (Diablomundo), 1993 September 16-19; (4 of 4); (Project Outline and Reports) (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - An Evening with Samuel Beckett (Bille Whitelaw), 1993 September 21; (Programs, PSAs, Press Clippings, and Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Our Asylum...Unfinished (Elena Jandova and Besmond Ondatje), 1993 November 22-23; (Production, Marketing, and Financial Materials) (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - American College Theatre Festival, Region IV, 1996 February 7-11; (Participation Requests and Correspondence) (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - Kennedy Center American College Theatre Festival, 1996 April 15-23; (Magazine and Financial Material) (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - The Trial (Project Istropolitana '96, Bratislava, Slovakia), 1996 June 21-July 2; (1 of 2); (Planning/Production Materials and Correspondence) (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - The Trial (Project Istropolitana '96, Bratislava, Slovakia), 1996 June 21-July 2; (2 of 2); (Financial Materials - Travel and Shipping) (Box 58, Folder 44)
    - The Gipsies (Academy of Theatre and Film, Bucharest, Romania), 1996 September 19-20; (Planning/Production Materials and Correspondence) (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - Phaedra and the Nurse (Theresa Dickinson and Ann Woodhead), 1997 April 15; (1 of 3); (Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 46)
    - Phaedra and the Nurse (Theresa Dickinson and Ann Woodhead), 1997 April 15; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - Phaedra and the Nurse (Theresa Dickinson and Ann Woodhead), 1997 April 15; (3 of 3); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - U.S./Hungarian Exhange Initiative (Third Alternative Theatre Festival, Budapest, Hungary), 1997 April 18-30; (1 of 2); (Programs and Brochures) (Box 58, Folder 49)
    - U.S./Hungarian Exhange Initiative (Third Alternative Theatre Festival, Budapest, Hungary), 1997 April 18-30; (2 of 2); (Production/Planning Materials) (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Cafe Budapest, Works of Contemporary Hungarian Writers (Peter Huszti), 1997 November; (1 of 3); (Programs) (Box 58, Folder 51)
    - Cafe Budapest, Works of Contemporary Hungarian Writers (Peter Huszti), 1997 November; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 52)
    - Cafe Budapest, Works of Contemporary Hungarian Writers (Peter Huszti), 1997 November; (3 of 3); (Negatives) (Box 58, Folder 53)
    - Patron Reception at the Orangery, 1998; (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 54)
    - Actor Training: International Perspectives, 1999 January 15-18; (1 of 2); (Event Materials, PSAs, and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 55)
    - Actor Training: International Perspectives, 1999 January 15-18; (2 of 2); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 56)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre Company 25th Anniversary Gala, 1999 October 8; (1 of 3); (Event Program and Invitations) (Box 58, Folder 57)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre Company 25th Anniversary Gala, 1999 October 8; (2 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 58)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre Company 25th Anniversary Gala, 1999 October 8; (3 of 3); (Photographs) (Box 58, Folder 59)
    - As You Like It (ACTER), 2000 September 22; (1 of 2); (Programs, Flyers, and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 60)
    - As You Like It (ACTER), 2000 September 22; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 61)
    - Caligula and Oedipus (Frank Hanig), 2000 September 30-October 1; (1 of 2); (Playbills and Press Clippings) (Box 58, Folder 62)
    - Caligula and Oedipus (Frank Hanig), 2000 September 30-October 1; (2 of 2); (Production Materials) (Box 58, Folder 63)
    - The Colored Museum (Strange Fruit On Stage Productions), 2002 April 3-7; (Production Materials) (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre Company 30th Anniversary Gala, 2004 September 12; (Invitation, Event Program, and Commemorative Keychain/Flashlight) (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - The Man Who Lives Here is Loony (R.B. Morris), 2005 April 10-11; (Playbill) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Macbeth (Actors from the London Stage), 2007 October 17-19; (Production Materials) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Clarence Brown Theatre Company 35th Anniversary Gala, 2009 September 20; (Event Program) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Other UT Theatre Special Events, 1982-1998; (Flyers and PSAs) (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Guest Contributors, 1982 March 29-1997; B; (Resume and Press Clippings)
    - Dr. Waldeo Braden, 1982 March 29-April 1; (PSAs) (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Maurice Daniels, 1987-1993; (CV and Obituaries) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Eva LaGallienne, 1974-1975; (Program and Press Clippings) (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Joshua Logan, 1975-1976; (Press Clippings) (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - John O'Keefe, 1997; (Photographs) (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Clarence Brown Theatre Contributors, circa 1970-1991; VI; (Press Clippings, Profiles, and Photographs)
  - Clarence and Marian Spies Brown, circa 1970-1990; A
    - General Press, 1972-1990 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Birthday Celebrations, 1980-1985; (Photographs and Negatives) (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Obituaries, 1987; (Memorial Programs and Press Clippings) (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Tributes, circa 1970-1977; (Photographs) (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - External Theatre Contributors, 1976-1991; B; (Profiles and Press Clippings)
    - Ula Love Doughty, 1976-1991; (Press Clippings, Photographs, Negatives, and Plaques) (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - David Keith, 1986-1987; (Press Clippings) (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Ellis Mayes, circa 1966 July-1993 June 4; (Photographs) (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Unidentified Photographs, circa 1974-2004; VII
  - Miscellaneous Party Photographs, circa 1990s; (1 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Party Photographs, circa 1990s; (2 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Party Photographs, circa 1990s; (3 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Party Photographs, circa 1990s; (4 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Party Photographs, circa 1990s; (5 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Party Photographs, circa 1990s; (6 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Portraits, circa 1974-2004; (1 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Portraits, circa 1974-2004; (2 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives, circa 1974-2004 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- Removed and Oversize Materials, circa 1901-2010 September 19; VIII; (Posters, Oversized Photographs, and Negatives)
  - Faculty Players, circa 1937; (Negatives) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Pride and Prejudice, circa 1942; (Negatives) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Lysistrata (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 February 11-16, 18; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - The Country Wife (Carousel Theatre), 1972 May 11-13, 16-19; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (1 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (2 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (3 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (4 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (5 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (6 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Loot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 June 16-17, 20-23; (7 of 7); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - The Gloaming, Oh My Darling (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 June 30-July 5, 7; (1 of 6); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - The Gloaming, Oh My Darling (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 June 30-July 5, 7; (2 of 6); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - The Gloaming, Oh My Darling (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 June 30-July 5, 7; (3 of 6); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - The Gloaming, Oh My Darling (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 June 30-July 5, 7; (4 of 6); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - The Gloaming, Oh My Darling (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 June 30-July 5, 7; (5 of 6); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - The Gloaming, Oh My Darling (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 June 30-July 5, 7; (6 of 6); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Any Wednesday (Carousel Theatre), 1972 July 14-15, 18-21; (1 of 3); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Any Wednesday (Carousel Theatre), 1972 July 14-15, 18-21; (2 of 3); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Any Wednesday (Carousel Theatre), 1972 July 14-15, 18-21; (3 of 3); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - 1776 (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 July 28-29, August 1-5; September 26-30, October 2-7; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - The Moon is Blue (Carousel Theatre), 1972 August 11-12, 15-18; (1 of 2); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - The Moon is Blue (Carousel Theatre), 1972 August 11-12, 15-18; (2 of 2); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Waiting for Godot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 October 11-15, 20-21; (1 of 3); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Waiting for Godot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 October 11-15, 20-21; (2 of 3); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Waiting for Godot (Carousel Theatre), 1972 October 11-15, 20-21; (3 of 3); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Tartuffe (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1972 November 8-18; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - The Wizard of Oz (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1973 January 31-February 10; (1 of 2); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - The Wizard of Oz (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1973 January 31-February 10; (2 of 2); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Leaves of Blue (Theatre 2), 1973 February 17-18; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - The Canterbury Tales (Carousel Theatre), 1973 April 13-28; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1944-1973; (1 of 2); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Other Play Photographs (Subjects Unidentified), circa 1944-1973; (2 of 2); (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - University of Tennessee Theatres Buildings, 1952-1975; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Portraits, circa 1974-2004; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Mayoral Recognition of UT Theatres Week, 1986 February 3 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Early University of Tennessee Play, circa 1901; (Oversize Photograph) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Charley's Aunt, circa 1942; (Related to Series V: Faculty Players, Subseries B: Plays); (Poster) (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Small Play Posters, 1975 October-1978 December (Box 61, Folder 3)
    General Note
    Includes Macbeth (October-November 1985), The Beaux' Stratagem (April 1978), Harvey (May 1978), The Taming of the Shrew (November 1978), and A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (November-December 1978).
  - Small Play Posters, 1979 February-November (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Includes The Hot L Baltimore (February-March 1979), Oh! What a Lovely War (October 1979), and Twelfth Night (November 1979).
  - Small Play Posters, 1986 May-1987 February (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Includes True West (May 1986), Beyond Therapy (October-November 1986), and Joe Egg (February 1987).
  - Small Play Posters, 1987 April-1988 March (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Includes Spring Awakening (April 1987) and To Clothe the Naked (February-March 1988).
  - Small Play Posters, 1989 February-March (Box 61, Folder 7)
    Includes Hunting Cockroaches (February-March 1989), Actors from the London Stage: Stoppard This Evening and King Lear (March 1989), and Have You Seen Zandile (March 1989).
  - Small Play Posters, 1989 April-October (Box 61, Folder 8)
    Includes Cloud 9 (April 1989), Godspell (July 1989), and Ceremonies in Dark Old Men (October 1989).
  - Small Play Posters, 1998 June-1999 March (Box 61, Folder 9)
    Includes Dancing at Lughnasa (June 1998), The Matchmaker (October 1998), A Christmas Carol (November-December 1998), Ghosts (January-February 1999), and A Midsummer Night's Dream (February-March 1999).
  - Small Play Posters, 1999 April-2010 September (Box 61, Folder 10)
    Includes Cabaret (April 1999), The Woman in Black (October 2000), Inherit the Wind (February 2001), The Rainmaker (August-September 2001), and Amadeus (September 2010).
  - Hunter Hills Homecoming '86, 1986; (Poster) (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Cotton Patch Gospel (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1994 October 14-29; (Related to Box 14, Folder 57); (Production Drawing) (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Stage and Production Designs, circa 2001 August (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - (2) Anthony Quayle Photos, circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Large Play Posters, 1973 November-1975 August (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Includes Measure for Measure (November 1973), The Tinker's Wedding (July 1974), Cabaret (August 1974), and Hunter Hills Season (July-August 1975).
  - Large Play Posters, 1975 October-1978 September (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Includes Macbeth (October-November 1975), When You Comin' Back, Red Ryder (March 1976), Woyzeck (November 1976), The Tax Collector (January-February 1977), and Flemming (September-October 1978).
  - Large Play Posters, 1979 February-July (Box 62, Folder 4)
    General Physical Description
    Includes A Meeting by the River (February-March 1979), As You Like It (March-April 1979), and A Horse of a Different Color (June-July 1979).
  - Large Play Posters, 1980 February-1981March (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Includes Night Must Fall (February 1980), The Physicists (March-April 1980), Candide (November 1980), and The Oldest Living Graduate (February-March 1981).
  - Large Play Posters, 1981 April-1982 December (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Includes Dracula: A Musical Nightmare (April 1981), An Italian Straw Hat (May 1981), Mr. Roosevelt's Train Never Got Here (November-December 1981), Streamers (October-November 1982), and The Miser (November-December 1982).
  - Large Play Posters, 1983 February-December (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Includes The Prime of Miss Brodie (February-March 1983), The Importance of Being Earnest (May 1983), Hay Fever (May-June 1983), Sweeney Todd (September-October 1983), and Romeo and Juliet (November-December 1983).
  - Large Play Posters, 1984 February-1985 April (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Includes Misalliance (February-May 1984), The Dining Room (May-June1984), Richard III (February 1985), and The Caretaker (March 1985).
  - Large Play Posters, 1985 April-1986 June (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Includes She Stoops to Conquer (April 1985), House of Blue Leaves (May 1985), Equus; The Rivals; Three Sisters (July-August 1985), The Vinegar Tree (March-April 1986), and Bus Stop (May June 1986).
  - Large Play Posters, 1986 November-1987 April (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Includes A Christmas Carol (November-December 1986), Present Laughter (January-February 1987), and The Harmful Effects of Tobacco (March 1987), and Macbeth (March-April 1987).
  - Large Play Posters, 1987 May-1988 February (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Includes Brighton Beach Memoirs (May-June 1987), The Man Who Came to Dinner (October 1987), Pygmalion (November-December 1987), and Master Harold and the Boys (January-February 1988).
  - Large Play Posters, 1988 March-October (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Includes The Diary of Anne Frank (March-April 1988), Man of Mode (April 1988), Amadeus (September 1988), and The Crucible (September-October 1988).
  - Large Play Posters, 1988 November-1989 April (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Includes Uncle Vanya (November 1988), A Christmas Carol (November 1988), Deja Vu (February 1989), and Noises Off (March-April 1989).
  - Large Play Posters, 1989 September-1990 October (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Includes Camille (September 1989), Steel Magnolias (October 1990), and To Kill a Mockingbird (October 1990).
  - Large Play Posters, 1994 November-2000 March (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Includes A Christmas Carol (November-December 1994), The Seagull (February-March 1998), and Hamlet (March 2000).
  - A Christmas Carol, undated; (Poster) (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Henry IV (Carousel Theatre), 1975 April 30-May 10; (Related to Box 6, Folder 113); (Stage Design) (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Night Must Fall (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1980 February 8-23; (Related to Box 8, Folder 62); (Set Design) (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Pygmalion (Clarence Brown Theatre), 1987 November 27-December 19; (Related to Box 12, Folder 75); (State and Set Designs) (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Anna Karenina (Ula Love Doughty Carousel Theatre), 2004 October 7-24; (Related to Box 22, Folder 20); (Stage Designs) (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Clarence Brown Theatre Physical Plans, 1974 March (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 1985 October 9-1993 February 19; (Includes Extremeties, Mr. Roosevelt's Train..., A Midsummer Night's Dream, You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown, Fanshen, The Heidi Chronicles, Albert Herring, 1776, Oliver, and The Marriage of Figaro.) (Box 64)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 1996 August 27-2000 September 10; (Includes Grease, The Matchmaker, Catfish Moon, Cinderella, and Dha Fuzion.) (Box 65)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 2000 December 4-2001 August 24; (Includes Inherit the Wind, The Glass Menagerie, and The Illusion.) (Box 66)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 2001 September 10-2005 September 5; (Includes A Child's Christmas in Wales, All in the Timing, Romeo and Juliet, and Arsenic and Old Lace.) (Box 67)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 2006 September 24-2007; (Includes The Laramie Project, Fences, Assassins, and A Flea in Her Ear.) (Box 68)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 2008 April 24-2009 January 30; (Includes The Marriage of Bette and Boo, The Triumph of Love, Ain't Misbehavin', and Tommy.) (Box 69)
  - Ground, Production, and Lighting Plans, 2009 October 19-2010 February 3; (Includes Charley's Aunt and The Man of La Mancha.) (Box 70)